Please insert coins.
Well, time to slowly get
crushed into oblivion.
Hold up!
It seems the nefarious Netherlord can't
see me, which only changes everything.
There we go.
Next up, I'll cleverly spend
the points I have left.
Guess who's good as new?
Small call.
These babies are used in dioramas,
and according to my research, they're
the smallest vending machines.
Boxxo is back!
Hopefully the nether dork
thinks I kicked the bucket,
but I'd better camouflage
myself just to be safe.
What in the heck?
Why'd he make a supersized
summoning circle?
Red alert!
That freak combined
all the Stratum bosses!
Ruh-roh, that means this mad
monster's packing peak power!
It's only a matter of time until
this whole place collapses!
Behold, as I entomb that foolish demon
lord and assert control over my own domain!
And that's how I wound up living
underground for four whole days.
I bunkered up with telekinesis
and concrete blocks,
plus flowers for a splash of color.
It sure is lonesome being
buried alive, but it's fine.
I know Lamas will give
it her all to find me.
Oh Lamas, you've come such a long way.
When we met,
other hunters thought you were useless and
you'd even been abandoned by your team.
I'm sure that must have
hurt like the dickens.
But check out your glow up.
Now you're an able hunter and a household
name in the clear flow lake stratum.
I've literally had your
back this whole time.
So just thinking about
it gets me all verklempt.
She told me we could
stay together forever.
Once this little mess is settled.
I have no doubt she'll help me conquer
another dungeon to become human again.
Seems the rest of the gang
wants to tag along too.
Road trip baby.
As long as I can keep adventuring with
this rowdy yet lovable band of misfits,
I've got no complaints.
Welp, time for the yuge.
I'll show these meanies what
vending machines are made of.
Come over there!
Fox Show!
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner, Lamas!
The name's Boxxo! Hello there!
That means yes, by the way!
My poison cry.
You can kill...
Oh...
I'm not put down...
I don't feel...
I really don't have a clue... Here...
I'm not gonna be a scene.
I'm not looking at vibe.
Don't go anywhere...
I'll have a lot of fun...
You can't...
If you let, you play...
The only time you got into the mode...
You can't lose...
I'm holding a dream self.
And I know what I have left.
I'm holding a dream in the dark.
I'm holding my head head.
I'm holding my head.
I'm holding my thigh.
What can I have left?
I'm holding my head.
Hello there.
That voice.
Bobco!
I'm on my way!
It's Lovas!
Bobco!
Hello there.
Bob, I knew it!
You hang in there, okay?
I'm digging you out!
Oh, phew, glad you're not squished.
Good to have you back.
Everyone's feeling worried sick about you.
We should have known you'd be just fine.
I missed you so much.
You're not broken, are you?
Or scratched up?
I was so... Honestly,
you're lucky to be in one piece,
but you don't always have
to push your luck, you know.
Yes.
We finally made it.
How's it going, Boxo?
Is it too soon to ask you
to dish out some snacks?
Boxo's been dug out, can you dig it?
I always knew you'd make
it out of this, okay, pal?
Beyond a shadow of a doubt!
Your humor leaves a lot to
be desired, Director Dog.
Hey, Boxo.
It's good to see you.
The directors are safe and sound,
but wait, where's the bear?
Well, it's every when.
Oh, all of our friends are safe.
Director Bear and the others are busy.
They're pursuing the monster horde.
Knowing my buddies are okay
is a huge load off my ram.
Now, time to get vending.
Seeing as how the town was destroyed,
there aren't a ton of food options.
This calls for a lavish feast.
Hello there.
There's plenty to go around, so
just wait your turn, everyone.
And remember, be fair.
Children and old people go first.
So don't try to cut the line.
Hello, everyone.
Want some free food?
Trust me, you're gonna flip
when you taste this stuff!
In the end, I doled out packaged prezis
until the wee hours of the morning.
Pretty sure we've got enough
boxo food to last a while now.
A job well done.
Since they're not gonna starve, we
can go catch up with the others.
I'm told Captain Carry Oil's family
went after the monster horde.
Meanwhile, Director Bear,
the guards,
Heavy, and Mishuel are in a mad dash to
beat the beasts to the fortified city.
You better make sure you take a
little break if you need to, Boxo.
I agree.
Just relax.
Live a little, Boxo.
Take your hands to yourself!
We know you've been through a lot,
so it's probably a good idea
to take it easy for a bit.
Oh, thank you.
They need to rest.
Those four stayed up all night with me.
But I won't stop till the job is done.
You never change, do you, kiddo? Huh?
Getting so old you wake up
early does have its perks.
My skin's not porcinum,
but aging's not so bad.
Collagen's overrated.
The senior squad came equipped.
He thinks they want to tag along.
Count me in too, big boy.
I'm getting fired up.
Guess they're coming
along for the ride too.
I hate getting up early.
You sound like a spoiled brat.
Splash some water on your face
and pull yourself together, boy.
I don't want to.
Our team will remain here.
We'll work on rebuilding the town. Nice.
Now I don't have to
worry about this place.
I know I'm leaving it in good hands.
Why do men always sneak
away in the morning?
We'll miss you, Boxo.
Lamy, please be careful out there.
Be sure to give him help for us.
Thank you. Sneak you.
Well, is everyone ready
to get going? Yeah!
Isn't it a tad silly to be
hiding behind a tree like that?
Oh, goodness.
I didn't think you'd be able to see me.
Pleased to make your acquaintance,
and I deeply apologize for all the
trouble my naughty son has caused you.
Who the heck are you?
And who's this alleged
son you're talking about?
Oh, how spicy.
Ribby's pernicious.
He's my little rascal, after all.
Uh, lady, not to be mean, but is
Ribby in the room with us right now?
When he was a child, he was
so quiet and mild-mannered.
Where do you suppose I went wrong
for him to turn out the way he did?
I almost forgot.
Little Ribby, I hear he goes
by a different name these days.
I think it was, oh, now I
remember, the Netherlord.
The Nether Mama showed up?
Talk about a plot twist.
I know kids like to rebel,
but I still can't believe he
experimented on his own mother to
get that skeleton body.
As if that weren't bad enough,
he also won't let me die.
How could he be so cruel?
He used his own mother as a test
subject for his twisted dark art.
Damn, Netherlord, I knew you were mega-scum,
but this is full-on psycho territory.
Of course, a mother's love is eternal,
so I forgive him for everything!
Now I'm the Thumb
General and I strike down
anyone who dares to stand in my son's way!
I'm a good mother!
Alright, so just to be clear,
are you gonna try and kill us?
Of course I am!
A mother's love is nothing
if it's not unconditional!
That's a lovely maternal
sentiment on paper,
but it doesn't entail aiding mass murder!
Seems to me you're a
sorry excuse for a mother.
When a child's misbehaving, it's a
mother's duty to smack some sense into us.
The situation you just described isn't
a mother's love, it's indulgence.
Don't say that!
How dare you condemn me when
I've given him everything!
Don't you fool see that I'm
the best mother there ever was?
Everyone in the world except
my ribby and me can die!
The apple didn't fall far from the tree.
There's clearly no point trying
to reason with the thumb general
Anyone who isn't fighting,
follow me to safety.
Did you think we'd let
you get away with this?
You cowards are ganging up on me!
It's inexcusable.
John, it's feeding time.
That looks like the summoning circle.
The netherlord used.
Pretty clear where this is going.
I've got a real bad feeling
about that summoning circle.
So watch your back.
Come on, gramps!
Could it really be that bad?
It could that mana is downright alien.
It may be a monster from another.
Holy Isekai!
What's that weird monster-shaped thing?
I've seen more than my fair share of
monsters here, but that thing's ridiculous!
Boxxo! Boxxo! Boxxo!
Boxxo?
Oh, wow!
You can leave this nasty fella to us.
We're all itching to get in on the action.
Once you get as old as we are, you're
too short on time to bother with fear.
I don't know, the two of you still
find ways to scare me occasionally.
It does get intense when
you two are arguing.
Oh yeah, now I'm doubly fired up.
The forces of justice
fighting back against evil?
Yeah, this is what dreams are made of!
Shimmer down.
Oh, things are getting hot in here.
Looks like these buggies like to
explode whenever you blast them.
Hey, what the hey?
If this becomes a war of attrition,
stamina could be a real problem.
If only I could distract our opponent
with some kind of elaborate display.
Wait, I'm a freaking vending machine!
I tend it up!
I, er, work!
Freddie!
The whole sky's sparkling!
Fireworks are always something special,
but there's nothing like
your very first time.
There's the big bug.
It's not really advancing,
but it's also facing away from
the fireworks, which means...
My hunch was right.
The Thumb General is the one
pulling its gross little strings.
Simply gorgeous. Lock it. Huh?
Did you need something, Boxo?
You hit it for O. Yup.
Now that I'm ranked three,
I can spawn concrete blocks
nearby instead of just under me.
So, um, you want me to throw these?
Hello there.
At the Thumb General. Yes.
Okay, you got it.
Success!
I turned into a cardboard vending
machine just before she threw it.
I won't get anywhere
near the thumb general.
No big.
I factored Lamas' bad
aim into the equation.
What the?
It's Bokshou!
They're so beautiful.
I wish I could watch them
with my little ribby.
Our defeat of the thumb general
calls for a victory dance.
But that would mean crashing
and burning, so maybe not.
Luckily, I have an exit strategy.
I should be in the clear now. Huh? Huh?
What's this weird Field feeling?
Boxo, you did something crazy again.
Sorry.
Don't think I'm gonna let you off
the hook just cause you're adorable.
Oh, the bug.
Is it vanquished or what?
Without its summoner
binding it to this world,
that beast went back from whence it came.
Textbook monster summoning.
That takes care of, well, the side
story, which still leaves the main plot.
We gotta hurry and
catch up to our friends!
Boom!
The mythical vehicle vending machine!
Famous amongst fellow
vending machine enthusiasts.
When the uninitiated behold its glory,
they often mistake it for a building.
Boxo, are you gonna give us another Acar?
Our party's gotten pretty bloated,
and the ground's not flat
like the everlasting stratum.
I've gotta take the bumpy
terrain into account.
Hmm, which means...
A pick-up truck!
That A-car looks different
from the last one.
Yeah, you're right.
It's definitely a lot
bigger than our old one.
It's so cool!
We like it!
A lot of these roads are uneven, so I know
dispensing a truck was the right call.
There's plenty of room
even with yours truly.
Since it's a foreign build, the
standard size is still huge.
I'm really starting to
like driving this thing.
I'm gonna go a little faster.
It's been a pleasant drive,
but it's almost lunchtime.
I wonder what I should
feed my friends today.
Ooh, I know just the thing.
My pals are in for a tasty treat.
Blammo!
A pizza vending machine baked to
order with all the right topics.
It's an authentic Italiano model.
Whatever it is looks good!
It's delicious!
Whoa, what is this crazy stuff?
You pull it apart and it gets so stretchy!
It was such a hit!
They ate it all in record time!
Don't hold out on us!
Pop out the good stuff already!
Hmm, someone's addicted, but
I only vend, I don't judge.
I'm so happy everyone loves my
hot and ready pizza so much!
Weird, they barely touched their zah.
Oh, snap!
It must be too heavy for their
ancient tummies to handle!
Thank you.
It's kind of you to
fuss over us like that.
The last thing was interesting,
but just a little too rich.
Thanks for thinking of us.
Though I hate to waste
perfectly good food. No worries.
Chewy, those are all
yours if you want them.
If I'm dreaming, you'll be here
till I'm done eating, okay?
Oh, Chewy, your stomach's
as bottomless as ever.
Just to be safe,
I'll load her up on lots of burgers and
fried chicken before we hit the road.
Hey, Boxel, can I have
one of those fizzy drinks?
Now what?
We need to devise a plan
to stop the Netherlord.
His powers are a pain in the
rear, but with all these points,
I wonder if I could use
my barrier to blow...
Hey, my tummy's feeling a little
angry, so how about a little snack?
I'll just wait to attack until his
tummy's angry. No, focus! Let's think.
Of the Finger Generals, I've defeated
the thumb and the middle fingy.
Ring finger General
Solrine switched sides.
That just leaves.
Boxo, I'm still starving over here!
The diabetes-inducing
sweetbread general... Dadnobbit!
I mean, the last two
generals will be tough.
The pinky general got away.
And there's no telling
where the forefinger...
I need something really sweet to help
wash down all that tasty food now.
Right.
Then there's the dreaded juice general.
Will you stop distracting me, Sweet?
I am this close to letting Hulemy
dissect your stomach for science!
I'm not getting any less thirsty.
Shwee's had enough sugar
to kill a grown elephant,
so let's try a zero-calorie beverage.
What is this?
There's something off
about the sweetness of it.
Tastes okay, I guess.
She not only eats a lot, but it seems
her sense of taste is also shockingly?
and annoyingly refined.
You're not thinking something
rude, are you, Boxo?
Gaining what?
Someone's gaining weight?
Me?
Is that what you're saying?
I'm in the middle of
a bulking phase, dude.
Fat Boxxo!
It's against the law to
talk about a girl's weight.
Got it?
Hello there.
The road trip went smoothly.
No accidents or illegal
fat comments to speak of.
It only took us a few days.
This contraption sure is handy.
I can see things in the far
off distance, clear as day.
Don't forget to revel
in the glory of vending!
Oh dear! Gramps!
No need to shout, I'm right behind you.
Up ahead, there's a standoff
against a horde of monsters.
Are you sure?
Let me have a gander.
It's serious.
I'm not loving their odds.
The poor saps are outnumbered.
If they're way out here, does
that mean what I think it does?
Hulemy, head right and make
this thing go even faster.
Got it.
It'll be my pleasure.
This is all kinds of bad.
They're completely surrounded.
With them packed so tightly together,
it would be too dangerous
to try a magic strike.
Pretty sure we'd try to set it to.
Oh, Shimei Lion Director Scorching
can't push the wind button?
I should probably tell Hulemy
to find somewhere safe to park.
All right, hold on to your butts, guys!
Hey, move it up!
I tried to warn ya.
I knew we'd find them here.
I should've known you'd show
up just in the nick of time.
Hurry, let's move the wounded
inside Boxo's Barrier.
If you can still move, carry
somebody who can't inside.
Don't worry, they're the good guys.
You're a lifesaver, Boxo.
You'll be okay.
I'll get you healed up in a jiffy.
Thanks a bunch. Cut.
Proceed with caution.
You as well, big sis.
Too hot to handle.
Big Bong!
Watching my friends commit acts of
violence reminds me how lucky I am.
They're OP compared to other hunters.
Looks like I don't mean
to bust out my arrows.
She's not wrong, but she's also not right.
Time to put that lazy tushy to work.
How do you gotta be so
mean, Boxo? Oh, Chewie,
didn't I teach you if you
have time to run your mouth,
you have time to pull your weight?
I know, you said it a lot!
Huh, is it just me or is
Chewie frightened of something?
Eh, I should stop dwelling on it.
Thus, the battle ended in victory.
Thanks to my friends laying the
smackdown on those jabronis,
the final battle is almost upon us.
Hey, Boxo, I could use a drink.
Hello there.
This is a great story.
I'll be like you for a long time.
I can tell you, I can't believe you.
I can tell you.
I can tell you?
Thank you.
I can tell you, I feel so good.
I feel so good.
Make a good make a round of moon make you